Hello.
こんにちは
I was really surprised.
すごい びっくりしましたね
Sorry, I called out to you all of a sudden.
ごめんね、ちょっといきなり声かかっちゃった
It's cute.
かわいいですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Her smile is so cute.
笑顔がめっちゃかわいい
You look so young, but are you wearing a lot of shoes now?
すっげー若そうだけど、今、多い靴ですか?
I'm 18 now.
今、18です
18?
You're very young.
めっちゃ若いじゃん
Oh no.
やば
Hey, 18 doesn't mean you're a high school student.
ちょっとさ、 18ってことは、 まさか高校生とかじゃないけど
hey.
ね
university student.
大 学生
I was surprised.
びっくりした
Good, good.
よかったよかった
So now that you're a college student, is it fun?
じゃあ今、大学生なんで、 楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいです
I like campus life.
いいね、キャンパスライフ
Universities are generally liberal arts,
大学は、 じゃあ、大まかに 文系、
If you're in science, this is it.
理系だったら、こっち
Humanities?
文系?
Just like the image.
イメージ通り
I think I'm reading some great poetry.
すごい詩とか読んでそう
What, you won't tell me?
え、言われない?
It sounds like you have that kind of romantic side.
なんか、そういう ロマンチストなところありそうだな
I told you that college was fun, friend.
大学楽しいって言ったけど、 友達、
Well, just in case, what about a boyfriend?
いや、一応、 彼氏とかは?
Fair enough.
まあまあ
Well, well.
まあ まあ
What, do you have a boyfriend?
え、彼氏いる?
Well, there are.
まあ、いるよね
Because it's cute.
可愛いからね
How many people are there?
何人くらいいるの?
Who?
何人?
I try to listen to it every time, but sometimes...
毎回聞くようにしてるんだけど、 たまに、
How many boyfriends do you have?
彼氏何人いるの?
When I said that, there were three of us!
って言ったら、 あ、3人です!
That being said, for a moment...
っていうことが言って、 ちょっと、
Uncle will be surprised.
おじさんびっくりするんだよね
Well, it's the same.
まあ、そりゃ一緒だよね
Have you been with your boyfriend for a long time?
彼氏とは長いんですか?
Isn't there?
ないのかな?
I don't know though.
分かんないけど
About a year.
1年とか
1年くらい
So, do you feel like you've been dating since then?
じゃあ、ここ時代から付き合ってた感じ?
That's right.
うんですね
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
That's not his first time, right?
それが初彼ではないよね?
Maybe.
たぶんね
Second person?
2人目?
Third person?
3人目?
2nd person.
2人目
nice.
いいね
It seems like an order, I guess.
順番っぽいね、なんかね
Well, now that's it.
じゃあ、今、あれだ
Wait, you and your boyfriend go to the same university?
え、彼氏とは同じ大学?
It's the same university.
同じ大学だよね
That's right.
そうなんだね
But that's it.
でも、あれだね
If we weren't at the same university, other boys would probably approach me.
同じ大学じゃねえだったら、他の男の子に声かけられそうだけど
hey.
ね
Why does that happen?
なん でそんなことあるの?
How many steps are you taking?
何歩とかされない?
It happens sometimes.
たまにされるっていう
It's because it's cute.
それは可愛いからされるから
Yeah.
うん
What, do you refuse properly?
え、ちゃんと断る?
Or maybe we can go out together?
それとも一緒に遊びに行ったりとかしちゃう?
No, I basically refuse.
いや、基本的に断る
That's it.
あれだね
You're single-minded, then.
一途なんだね、じゃあ
Like, kind of.
いいね、なんか
Cute and dedicated, that's the ideal of an old man.
可愛くて一途ってなんか、 おじさんの理想だよね
Yeah.
うん
By the way, have you ever had a boyfriend?
ちなみに彼氏とは、 経験済みですか?
Eh, one night.
え、一夜
I have already experienced this with my boyfriend, so has anything changed?
彼氏と経験済みで、 何か変わったところでした?
Do you have any experience?
経験とかあります?
do not have.
ない
Eh, just a house or something?
え、なんか家とかだけ?
Just the house.
家とかだけ
Lately, I've been hearing a lot about things like manga cafes.
最近よく聞くのが、 漫画喫茶とか、
In the car or outside.
車の中とか、 外とか
Oh, not at all.
あ、全くないんだ
So having a boyfriend is normal, right?
じゃあ、彼氏はノーマルなことなんだね、
See you then.
じゃあね
On the other hand, I would like to try something like this.
逆に、こういうところでやってみたいな、
Is there no such thing as a wish?
みたい な願望とかない?
I've never really thought about that.
特にそんな思った、 考えたことないな
That's it.
あれだね
I don't have that much experience, so I guess I don't really understand that kind of thing.
そんなに経験がないから、 あんまそういうの分からないなのか、
Do you really think that a plain position is enough?
本当になんか、 淡 白な位置で十分って思ってるのか、
Which one?
どっち?
I know you don't have any experience.
経験がないかそういうのは分かって
Well, from now on, I'll be 18.
じゃあ、これから、 18だしね
As I continue to experience more and more,
これからどんどん経験していけば、
Maybe something like this is good.
こういうのがいいっていうのがあるのかもしれない
Well, if you don't really have that much experience.
じゃあ、わりと経験が そんなにないって感じなんだったら
So what about women?
じゃあ、女にとかは?
I've never done it alone.
私って一人でしたことないです
picture?
え?
At all?
まったく?
Not even once.
一回もないね
I'd like to tinker with it myself, use some tools, etc.
自分でいじったりとか、 なんか 道具あてたりとか、
So you don't have any tools anymore?
じゃあもう道具も持ってないの?
I don't know much about tools,
道具とかあんまそんなに詳しくないし、
I don't really understand.
あんま分かんない
Of all the people Ori-san has met so far,
なんか、わりと、 今までおりさんが会ってきた中では、
That's rare.
珍しいね
Saying "I won't do it to a woman" or "I've never done it before" is so lame.
女にしませんとか、 やったことないですっていうのがあんまいな
Because it was hot.
かった から
On the contrary, it's a bit refreshing.
なんか、逆に新鮮だわちょっと
So, what part of your body should I touch to feel good?
じゃあ、自分の体どこ触ったら気持ちいいとかって、
Feel like you don't really understand?
あんま分からない感じ?
I don't really understand.
あんま分かってない
When I was with my boyfriend, there was something about it that felt so good.
彼氏としているときに、 これ気持ちよかったみたいなのがある
It felt good to have my breasts licked.
なんか胸舐められたのが気持ちよかったとか
Oh, really?
あ、本当?
You don't have much experience.
経験があんまないんだね
You don't really understand.
あんま分かってないね
Today we will focus on that.
今日はそこらへんを、 重点的に
I chose various places and tried licking various places,
いろんなところを選んで、 いろんなところを舐めてみたら、
You might understand.
分かるかもしれない
So, let's do some things.
じゃあ、ちょっといろいろやっていこうか
Were you surprised when you first saw this?
最初、これ見たときびっくりしたでしょ?
I'm going to have sex with this person today.
今日、この人とセックスするんだ
That's fine.
そんなんでいいのね
そんなんでいいの
I guess that's just how everyone is.
たぶんね、じっちゅはくみんなそんなんで
Are you really nervous?
わりと緊張してる?
I'm a little nervous.
少し緊張は
Are you nervous?
緊張してらっしゃる?
Now, Kotchihine.
今、ことっちひね
I've never been disappointed.
おめられたことない
Beautiful things.
き れいなことっちひね
nice.
いいね
The reaction is cute and nice.
反応かわいくていいね
It was fun, wasn't it?
楽しかったよね
Only the old man had fun.
おじさんだけ楽しかったね
Can I have you stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってもらっていい?
Isn't it very thin?
めっちゃ細くない?
Try cueing it yourself.
自分でキューってやってみて
It's extremely thin.
めちゃくちゃ細いね
Not told?
言われない?
I've been told that, but it's not really close.
言われはするけど、あんま近くはない
Oh, it's not nearby.
あ、近くはないんだ
There's nothing nearby.
近くはない
I'm only about half as tall as my uncle.
おじさんより半分くらいしかないんだよ
This is only half the size of my uncle.
これはね、おじさんより半分しかない
Uncle, this is what it is.
おじさんこれだからね
Are you doing any exercise?
運動とかしてる?
I haven't done anything in particular.
特にはしてない
Isn't it the sports club?
運動部じゃない?
It wasn't an athletic club, at all.
運動部じゃなかったもん、全然
I feel toned.
引き締まってる感じがする
I wonder if I'm an athlete if I exercise.
運動とかやったらアスリートなのかしらって
Where it comes out.
出るところに
A great old man is touching me.
すごいおじさん触ってくるじゃん
I was surprised.
びっくりしたね
I have a habit of touching things naturally.
ナチュラルに触るのが癖なんすよ
I really like your smile.
本当に笑顔がいいね
I'm glad you laughed.
笑ってくれるうれしい
I don't know what to do.
どうすればいいのかわからない
amazing.
すごい
Breasts Namiko?
胸なみこ?
That's fine.
いいです
Just in case.
一応
It's fine just in case.
一応いいわ
I'm glad you laughed.
笑ってくれるうれしいんだな
I think it's very simple.
すごいシンプルにした気ですね
I only wear simple things.
シンプルなものしか履かないから
On the other hand, it's through the nose.
なんか逆に鼻からとかです
That's what I'm saying, but it may be exactly as you imagine.
こう言っちゃうんだけど、イメージ通りかもしれない
Wow, this kind of thing suits me.
すごい、こういうのが似合う感じ
That's a lie.
嘘ね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
That's because only Buntz appears.
それはね、 バンツだけ出てるからね
It makes me laugh.
笑っちゃうよね
Do you like to laugh too?
おじさんも笑っちゃうの好きなのかな?
Cut your butt.
お尻を切って
Please pose Nana.
ナナをポーズしてください
Cross your legs.
足を組んで
Please take my feet.
足を受けてください
And stick your butt out.
で、お尻を突き出す
That's my butt.
お尻をそう
Your body is soft.
体柔らかいね
This is muscular.
これ筋肉質だよね
Surprisingly.
意外と
You have a nice butt.
いいお尻してますね
Nice ass.
いいお尻
I hope it becomes a simple seamless part.
シームレスのシンプルパーツとなったらいいな
Uncle, please bite into that.
おじさん、それ食い込ましてくださいね
Your smile is beautiful, so I want you to laugh a lot.
笑顔が素敵だから、 いっぱい笑ってほしい
Your butt is really beautiful.
本当にお尻きれいだね
I'm so surprised.
驚きすぎる
a little bit...
ちょっと...
It just smelled a bit.
ちょっと匂い感だっただけ
It smells really good though.
すごい良い匂いしますけど
It seemed surprising.
驚きそうだったね
Maybe I've gained confidence.
自信来たかも
Really.
本当に
Open your legs.
足を開いて
It looks like you'll have to chew on it a lot.
すごく噛んでおさそうだけど
Still not touching it yourself?
それでも自分で触らないの?
I think it's probably better to bite,
たぶん噛んだほうが良い方だと思うけど、
I think I'll try it myself.
自分で触ろうとは思う
Don't you want to touch it?
触ろうとは思わないの?
I don't think I'll touch it.
触ろうとは思わない
Shall I pull it out?
抜いちゃおうか
wonderful.
素晴らしい
nice.
いいね
Simple and beautiful.
シンプルにきれい
And clean off-sage.
そして、オフセージにきれい
4 A woman is cleaning inside the backfire trace.
4女性が裏目のトレースの中できれいにしてる
What should I do?
どうしよう
Insert your arm and put your arm behind your back.
腕を挿して、 腕を後ろにやる
I puff out my chest.
胸を張る
It's really big.
すごく大きいですね
Aren't you hiding it?
隠してない?
big.
大きい
Raise your arms a little more.
もうちょっと腕を上げて
Is the pigment or hair naturally thin?
元々色素とか毛が薄いのかな?
reverse.
逆
reverse?
逆?
Maybe this is the raw liver.
もしかしたらここが生肝体かもしれない
No, no.
違う違う
Maybe.
かもしれない
So maybe.
だから、かもしれない
Maybe.
かもしれない
Amazing body.
すごい体が
odor.
臭い
Then sit down.
じゃあ座って
Sit down.
座って
Same pose.
同じポーズ
The face has decreased.
顔が減って
Was it raw liver?
生肝体だった?
It tickled me.
くすぐったやった
It tickled me so much.
すごいくすぐった
I see.
そうか
disappointing.
残念
It might have been better if it was a raw liver.
生肝体だったらよかったかもしれない
I was already halfway through my uncle's death.
もうちょっとおじさんの死に半分くらい入ってたけど
So beautiful.
めっちゃきれい
I'll praise you right away.
すぐ褒めるけど
You have it, right?
持ってるでしょ
I thought about it for a moment.
ちょっと思った
disappointing.
残念
Isn't it so beautiful?
めちゃくちゃきれいじゃない?
Above all, I'm a sucker for new rings.
何よりさ、 ニューリングペチだもんね
New Ring is so beautiful.
ニューリングめちゃくちゃきれいねん
This way?
こっち?
Surprisingly here?
意外とこっち?
Some people are a bit rowdy.
ちょっと乱暴な方がいる
I don't know.
わかんない
My boyfriend may be stronger than me.
割と彼氏の方が強いかもしれない
Hard.
ハードめ
Maybe.
もしかして
I just heard about it and got excited.
ちょっと聞いて、 興奮してきました
light.
軽い
It's light even though I have it.
持ってるのに軽い
This is easy, so I'm embarrassed.
これはカンプリなんで、 恥ずかしが出てる
It was a big shake.
すごいブレたね
It's blurry.
ブレてる
Why do you hide it?
なんで隠すの?
Obviously, there are fewer colors.
明らかに、 色が少なくなってますけど
Does this smell make you angry?
これ、匂いから怒る?
get angry
怒る
Don't do anything unpleasant.
嫌なことしないで
In this state, spread it out.
この状態で、 広げてください
Spread it?
広げ?
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃきれい
Show me as it is.
そのまま見せてよ
A very beautiful pink color.
めっちゃきれいなピンク色
lie?
うそ?
It's really tight.
めっちゃきつい
lie?
うそ?
Mango is tough on this one.
マンゴーきついね、これ
lie?
うそ?
Even today, my tail is getting worse.
しっぽり今日でもなってきました
I say it often.
よく言う
regrettable.
悔しい
I'll realize it next time.
今度気づけるもんね
Several times, I went to Mento and said erotic things.
何度かメント向かって、 エロいと
Don't say it to me.
メント向かって言われないで
Because it's not said much.
あんまり言われないから
Don't be erotic.
エロいしないで
It's kind of erotic.
なんかエロいな
Erotic.
エロい